Once upon a time,
there was a railway company that kept using Windows XP.
And it became a plaything for black-hat hackers.
Yes, that was our company five years ago.
And now...
CIO!
Windows 7 support ends in one month!
Approve the budget immediately!
...But we don't have any money.
...
I'm getting deja vu here.
We do have money, actually.
You know our bestselling ponzu sauce from the side business?
The profits from that can cover the monthly license fees.
Even so, there's this thing called departmental budgets...
Then if the System Division sells it and books the revenue,
we can secure the budget, right?
Tarumi-senpai is already setting it up.
You can't do that!
Sales will get mad at us!
...Fine, I get it.
I'll approve the budget, so stop doing weird things.
And that's how internal politics work.
At long last, the OS upgrade project began.
Well, we had already resolved
a lot of bugs in our virtual test environment, so--
All that's left is to deploy to the actual machines.
!?
It won't boot no matter what we do?
The cause was a CPU too old to support the NX bit.
Two days until support ends.
Unexpected issues kept popping up, and we fought to resolve them.
A 16-bit application won't run, they say.
Ugh... We'll have to use the 32-bit version of Windows 10 as an exception.
Six hours left.
The web app's layout is broken, they say.
Shall we add an "X-UA-Compatible" HTTP header?
30 seconds left.
Akane! You look terrible!
You should go home already.
I'm sorry... I don't think I can be of help anymore.
The last bug...
...resolved.
After 55 hours of continuous work,
the task was finally complete.